# **KAROL** STĘPIEŃ

+48 603 662 155 karol.stepien@me.com carste.pl github.com/carl-st linkedin.com/in/carl-st

## **ABOUT**

Since the beginning of my career working in the international environment. Each day trying to improve both hard and soft aspects of software development in order to get the most out of the time spent working. Mostly dealing with JS technologies but had quite some experience in native iOS development as well.

Tech nerd, car enthusiast, casual gamer.

Speaking Polish? Check out my podcast -Glosariusz Programisty

Speaking English? Check out my YouTube series - Developer Glossary

Links available on carste.pl



Located in Kraków, Poland Born 07/11/1994

Speaking advanced English (C1) Learning German and Spanish<sup>\*</sup>

## EXPERIENCE

12.2018 - Currently Senior Full Stack Engineer Ringier Axel Springer

Tech Kraków, Poland Taking part in development of six Swiss sites. Direct contact with client, relationship building.

React SSR, Redux, GraphQL, TypeScript, Node.js, AWŚ

## 07.2017 - Currently

Freelancer Carste IT Remotely

Websites, webapps and shops development. Polish clients.

Vanilla JS / React / Next.js, Electron, PWA, Wordpress, Shoper

#### 07.2017 - 12.2018 Front-End Developer

Future Processing Gliwice, Poland

SmartCity solution development. Direct contact with French client.

React, Redux, REST, JSON-LD

#### 07.2016 - 11.2016

iOS Developer Yattsi Communications Remotely

Travelling app development. Direct contact with Venezuelan client.

Native iOS Swift application

#### 09.2015 - 05.2016

iOS Developer BCG Digital Ventures Remotely

Mobile service-for-hire apps development. Direct cooperation with US client.

Native iOS Objective-C and Java Android applications

#### 07.2015

iOS Developer Internship Gorrion Software House Gliwice, Poland

Invoice management app development.

Native iOS Swift application

# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2018

M.Eng, Computer Science Silesian University of Technology

Master thesis: "Intelligent monitoring of sleep quality using lot technology in the Microsoft Azure cloud."

Azure ML vs. CreateML + CoreML Apple Watch and iOS Swift apps using trained Random Forest model

### 2013 - 2017

B.E., Computer Science Silesian University of Technology

Engineering thesis: "Mulitplatform appointment management system."

MongoDB, Express.js, Angular 2, Node.js (MEAN) Web Application iOS Cliént written in Swift

## TECH

React (SSR) Redux Next.js TypeScript Node.is GraphQL

Nest.js (basics) Angular (basics)

**AWS** Vercel Netlify Jenkins CircleCI TravisCI

Swift & Objective-C

ios sdk